(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION INTENDED FOR
VIEWERS WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
We have no obligation
to introduce ourselves,
but I'll make an exception, so listen up.
We are the ones who bring down the hammer
on all loveless, perverted sex.
The Anti-Copulation Force.
Eh?
The NLNS.
N-NLNS?
What's that?
It's obviously short for No Love, No Sex...
Jun?
Jun!
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements, rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate, don't ever stop
Destroy it, make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
For the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
Fumino Kotoyose was taken
by the Anti-Copulation Force.
How do you plan to explain this?
We deeply apologize.
What were you all doing
with so many people gathered?
I can't waste funds
on incompetents like you.
I will suggest to Hitoura-sama
to cut the FS personnel.
Your every move is being checked.
Don't you forget it, you shitty XXX!
What is Ikuko's condition?
Her life is not in danger,
but she has huge XXX-shaped bruises
in her vagina and cervix.
She's lost her recent memories
due to the shock of being hit by the truck.
Then she probably
doesn't remember the identity...
of the Anti-Copulation Force either.
For Ikuko's sake, we must capture...
and send them to the Guillotine.
Otherwise...
we'll lose our home.
But they are formidable.
If our personnel is reduced,
capturing them
will become even more difficult.
How about we increase it instead?
Our squads.
It hurts.
My whole body hurts.
The inside of my back hurts like hell!
Big Bro's body is falling apart...
It's been like that since he woke up.
Give me more morphine!
If we inject any more,
you'll become a brain-dead addict.
Give it to me.
I heard you woke up.
How are you feeling?
Oh, Fumino.
I'm fine now.
Stop showing off.
Shut up.
Once again, Tachibana-sama,
thank you so much for saving us.
We are deeply grateful.
T-Thank you.
During the sport-gasm festival too.
It's not just about saving you.
I heard you are the key
to crush the Perverted Ordinance.
Am I wrong?
I don't know myself.
But if someone says so,
then that possibility is quite likely.
Either way,
in the end, we were the ones
who were saved.
Then,
big brother, as I thought,
your virginity...
Virginity?
Jun had a rough past.
Due to various circumstances,
he became impotent with a XXX complex.
But he was forced to get an erection.
Probably against his will.
Is it okay to laugh?
No.
By my standards,
if there's mucous membrane contact,
you're no longer virgin.
Which means I'm also...
no longer a proud virgin.
Junnosuke Tachibana is dead.
Poor Big Brother.
Well, you know.
If you were forced to get an erection,
it doesn't count, right?
Is that so?
That's right.
How should I put it...
After all, sex needs love, right?
I see.
You're right.
That's right.
Only when a man ejaculates from his heart
does he truly lose his virginity.
- That's right! That's it!
- So gullible.
- My pride is... still alive!
- Such gullible.
Beyond gullible.
Ta-da!
This is...
Well, it's like a welcome party
and a rally.
A welcome party?
Embarrassingly, we're also virgins,
so we were hoping to join you guys.
We look forward to working with you.
Well then, shall we have our leader
give a toast?
Woo-hoo! Leader!
We are...
comrades with a shared goal.
We've been oppressed by lewdness
and on the run,
let's fight back.
From now on...
No, now is the time.
Yeah.
By defeating the evil known as lewd sex,
we will live for true love.
That is our purpose of NLNS,
No Love No Sex!
Yeah!
Just a few days ago,
it was just me and Asa-chan,
huddling together...
enduring the pressure of lewdness.
Uhm...
"No Love No Sex" means
if there's no love, it's not sex,
which is a very shallow meaning.
Hehe, let him be.
Tachibana-kun, you're bad at English,
aren't you?
Mmph, mmph.
I will protect these comrades
from the evil hands of lewdness.
No matter what it takes.
I hope there are some promising candidates.
Rei, look at this.
Touka-sama, what is this?
I've deduced about the shape
of the object inserted into Ikuko.
The Vagina Profiling System.
To think it was completed.
Even so, this shape...
It's shaped to reap vaginas, isn't it?
Amazing... Its size, radius, hardness...
It's the golden ratio itself.
Truly a one-in-190-million dick.
If we can connect
this dick to the guillotine,
we won't need Fumino-san anymore.
Well done, you warriors.
I'll give you further orders
on Fumino Kotoyose's handover later.
Handover?
Eh, Fumino-chan is leaving?
No way, we just had a party for her.
Fumino, do you know this person?
I haven't met them,
but I have an idea.
Who are they?
I cannot say for sure,
but they are likely blood relatives.
If they were looking for a blood relative,
then it makes sense.
Then what about being
the key to crush the ordinance?
It seems Fumino-chan was living
in hiding before coming to us.
Alone in an old shrine.
There must be some
complicated circumstances.
But if you have a place to return to,
we'll help you get there, Fumino.
Yeah.
But FS won't just stand by, right?
What if big brother gets fucked again?
No doubt, FS is strong.
But we can make use of that strength!
THERE IS NO FUTURE FOR FS'S BRUTAL TYRANNY!
If we know the enemy's movements,
the success rate of the handover
should increase dramatically.
Jun.
To disrupt them from the inside,
it's not a bad idea
to jump into the lion's den.
No way.
We're going to penetrate FS.
MINOTSUKI ACADEMY
He's a really good boy.
I guarantee it.
Recruitment is already over.
But if you say so.
I-It's you...
The Royal Dick!
Royal Dick?
Junnosuke Tachibana.
I wish to enlist.
Don't joke around.
The FS has no need for the likes of you.
Please.
My sister's a net addict,
I need money for her treatment.
What?
Come on, Rei-chan, please.
Well...
I guess it's okay
to let him take the enlistment training.
I've been training my body daily.
I'm confident in my stamina.
Oh. Then prove it by
passing the enlistment training.
If you can keep up, that is.
Line up!
I'm your instructor, Rei Tadasugawa.
Don't open your XXX unless
you're spoken to or performing XXX!
And put a "sir"
before and after you spit out XXX.
Got it?
Sir, yes, sir!
I do not discriminate.
Impotent, short-dicked,
premature ejaculator,
gross groin, huge labia...
No matter what, I will treat you the same.
Because you are all equally
worthless sperm!
Sir, yes, sir!
I will raise you into respectable sperm
that won't be ashamed to creampie someone!
I will wrap useless sperm in a condom,
and eliminate it from our beloved FS.
That is my duty.
Understood?
Sir, yes, sir!
You there, your stance is sloppy.
It's the same as sex.
If your dick isn't erect
with proper posture,
you can't ejaculate.
Sir, yes, sir!
You there.
What's with that condom-like belt?
State your name.
Sir, I am Shuu Nakamura, sir!
For a mere XXX,
don't you dare use a human-like name!
From now on, you are Schubert.
Got it, Mozart?
Sir, yes, sir!
Su! Su!
And you are Susuko!
Sir.
Do you know why?
Sir, yes, sir, su!
Don't pant unless it's during sex!
Are you imitating a porn star?
Sir, no, sir!
For someone who can't even get up,
Tachibana is a waste of a name.
Nekobana suits you better.
Sir, yes, sir!
I'm returning the aptitude test results.
FS ENLISTMENT TEST RESULTS
You have leadership aptitude?
Nekobana.
A useless person
with no social or cooperative skills,
who is fundamentally unsuited for work,
is often said to have "creator aptitude."
Sir, yes, sir!
Having "leadership aptitude"
is the same thing.
You're the garbage of society,
a piece of trash, and scum!
Remember that, you incompetent creator!
Sir, yes, sir!
So annoying.
I'll cook you a meal
that's good for physical fatigue.
True or false question.
When climaxing from lewd sex,
you must moan with an "oho" voice.
True.
The answer is false.
You must also moan with an "oho" voice
even when you're not climaxing.
Damn it.
Is that DMV trick question?
Tachibana-san,
I'm applying the Hip Erotic Bandage.
This will make you yelp.
Ahh... Hotori...
Please relax your anus.
I-It feels good.
What is that? My head feels fuzzy.
Opp, Nanase-san's brain is being fried!
It's called NTR.
I can't possibly
let you do this for my sake after all.
No, I'm the one who can't forgive FS.
Because they called me Nekobana.
- Cause you are impotent.
- Cause you can't get erect.
I'll show them.
I'll make that instructor see that
I'm essential!
Nukitashi.
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
Su, su, su... Su, su, su...
I-I can't squirt any more, suu!
You can't serve in the FS
if you chicken out...
after squirting just once or twice.
Strive to be able to have
19 consecutive orgasms!
Y-Yes, ma'am, suu!
A XXX this tight is not in my data...
I'm cumming.
Not "I'm cumming",
but "Get pregnant, now!"
You XXX over there.
If all you do is moan "an an,"
even a women's magazine could do that!
So the time's come.
- The Sex-Production Training...
- Yes, one more time!
Yes, sir.
What's wrong?
This is also FS's job.
You should join in quickly.
Half-assed excuses
won't work on the instructor.
Then, as planned...
I am impotent.
Impotent?
Here's the medical certificate.
This is indeed...
In that case, XXX or XXX.
My skin is too sensitive so I can't.
I'm allergic to XXX juice.
Huh?
Then why did you ask me
to have sex during the sport-gasm festival?
Is it wrong for an impotent man
to want sex?
That's discrimination!
Impotent discrimination!
To say something so provocative
in this day and age...
To make it up, you must overcompensate me!
You bastard, that's enough...
Hold on, Rei.
Senpai.
May I confirm something?
Confirm?
Hey...
Lately, I've been getting erections
strangely easily.
Why?
Since when?
I am the leader of NLNS.
This level of pleasure is nothing!
Oh my, so it's true.
Normally, you would get rock hard.
When it comes to aphrodisiac effects
stronger than Touka-sama's...
only Ikuko comes to mind.
Since I'm impotent,
there's nothing you can do?
Mmm...
I'll overcompensate you.
You have a sick sister, right?
PHYSICAL LABOR
Instead, I'll work you to the bone.
Got it?
Sir...
Sir, yes, sir!
Wow, that looks delicious, hame.
This the rubbing pleasure bowl made of
juicy abalone and hard rock shellfish.
If you say "It looks fucking delicious!"...
You can swap your side of pickles
for a dick for free, hame.
What are you spacing out for?!
Your dick can't even get hard.
I hate discrimination and impotence.
Work your ass off.
She's a walking contradiction.
But the fatigue
from training is getting to me.
If I let my guard down,
I'll lose consciousness.
Nekobana-paisen, here you go.
Dried squid.
If you chew it,
you won't fall asleep.
And it smells like semen,
so you won't get caught.
Oh, that helps.
Susuko?
Su.
Ah, that...
What button is that?
Ah, this is...
It's a Moan Button.
According to my data, it was...
huge trend
on Seiran Island a few years ago.
You are...
Schubert, right?
Yeah. Pleasure to meet you,
Nekobana-kun.
There's nothing not in my data.
I grew up on Seiran Island,
so I know it well.
You grew up on Seiran Island?
Then do you know
a quiet girl with brown hair?
She's a kid who transferred out
in the middle of her time in C-Class.
Hmm...
Sorry, she's not in my data.
Is she an acquaintance of yours, Banapai?
Yeah.
Long time ago,
when I was on Seiran Island,
she was the only friend I was able to make.
We came to check on Tachibana-kun...
But he seems to be doing quite well.
You two, where is Katagiri-san?
Next on Street XXX-view...
is this person who was nearby, hame.
No, I'm...
Amazingly, this person...
has won first place
two years in a row for "Most Amazing XXX."
It's the Legendary XXX,
Nanase Katagiri!
Ah, um, hahaha, nice to meet you.
Speaking of Nanase-san,
she's famous for having a XXX
that connects all the way to outer space.
So how do you take care of your XXX?
Basically, with a XXX bucket relay.
Hey, hey, hey!
What a fine woman.
Let me screw you too.
It's a yakuza.
They're called
"anti-social forces" these days.
Never mind the term, Katagiri-san is...
I want to try it once
in front of the camera.
Hey, film this.
Excuse me.
The show has a schedule to follow.
Say what? Are you messing with me?
In middle school, I sent 20 of those
shitty delinquents to the hospital.
I'm Hashimoto from Class 2!
Hiyah!
Just so you know, I'm also
in the SHO's Special Combat Unit.
I was moved to public relations
because I'm too beautiful...
but I won't lose to an amateur.
Everyone, we apologize for the
inappropriate content earlier.
I'll take this.
Ah, a gat.
You should at least say "pistol."
That uses ammunition
made for the Special Combat Unit,
its power is no different from a real gun!
Help! A man is holding a gun!
You're a Special Combat Unit member, right?
So noisy.
If you don't shut up,
I'll shoot this girl... this creepy mascot.
Making fun of me? You stupid bird!
I'm Hashimoto from Class 2.
What's with that crazy guy?
What do we do, squad leader?
Calm down, it's time
for meat shield tactic.
You crazy bitch!
Eh?
Ah, no...
Who the hell are you?
Looks like you wanna die.
If I move carelessly,
Nanase will be in danger.
I have to distract him.
Huh? This sound is...
I used to do it in middle school,
the fountain of fucking.
Now is the time!
Y-You bastard...
Crap!
This life-or-death situation
is making my dick hard again.
Jun.
Nekobana-san.
Banapai!
Are you okay?
Thank goodness.
We were worried.
Was that you?
The trainee who rashly jumped out
and provoked the mob.
One mistake
and it could have been a disaster.
You are not fit to be in FS.
State your name.
I...
Sir su!
I am Susuko.
I overlooked the suspicious person.
Therefore, we are also complicit.
You guys...
Eh, I'm not to blame, am I?
Due to the trainee's blunder,
we've caused trouble for SHO.
Tadasugawa.
- What kind of training did you...
- But to begin with...
director Senba had her handgun stolen.
Sorry, I'm always so absent-minded.
Loading a riot gun during PR activities
is also a rule violation.
If you stop now, we can call it even.
Submit a report! Due today!
Instructor Tadasugawa.
Your split-second decision wasn't bad.
And neither is your shooting.
Tachibana.
I'm glad he's safe.
Heh, a yakuza?
I wanted to fight him for my rehab.
But that trainee, huh...
He seems quite quick-witted.
Might be a good fit for Squad 1.
Heh, whatever.
He's probably weaker than me, though.
Found you.